wedding-flowers-and-reception-ideas.com 2013-05-22

# Privacy Policy

| 

Last Revised 3/13/2009

Your use of **www.wedding-flowers-and-reception-ideas.com** (“Website”) constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions. This Website is produced by **Floral and Photo Art by Louann** (“Service Provider”). This policy does not cover information collected on sites linked to from the Website. This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the **Privacy Policy**. 

It is the goal of my Website to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. The following is a summary of the various ways I treat the information you provide me while using my site.

**THE TYPE OF INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS**

The Website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. When you complete a question form, make a purchase, subscribe to any publication(s), or register for any portion of my services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your wedding date or other information may be required.

 **HOW THE WEBSITE USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

Service Provider uses information you supply through the Website to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you make a purchase from our store website, **www.weddingflowersandreceptionideas.com** , I may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you the product order. 

Service Provider does not sell users' e-mail addresses. I do **NOT** share e-mail addresses and sell or share all other information with any other affiliates or companies. The only time you receive an e-mail from me is when you ask a question, place an order or request to be put on a web newsletter.

I also allow access to my database by third parties that provide me with services, such as technical maintenance but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. And if you choose to purchase items through features on my site, I may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment. 

There are also times when you provide information about yourself to me in areas of the site that are managed or participated in by third parties, such as Google Ads or shopping areas (links that take you to another website selling goods). In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third party(ies), each pursuant to its own policies. I may also provide your information to my advertisers (such as Google AdSense), so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While Service Provider will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, Service Provider does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

There may also be occasion when I am legally required to provide access to my database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose. 

**COOKIES**

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. I may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. 

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don't want any cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly. 

I may also use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the Website. These vendors use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements.

In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not mine and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

If you do not want the benefits of these advertising cookies, you may opt-out by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.IP ADDRESSYour Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website. 

**KIDS AND PARENTS**

Although there is not - nor ever will be - anything intentionally offensive on my website, it is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases or asking questions on this site. 

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so. If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator thru our "Contact Me" page.If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail me at my ["Contact Me"](http://www.wedding-flowers-and-reception-ideas.com/Contactme.html) section of the website.. I welcome your questions and feedback.

 **Additional Note: Google Adsense**

If you elect to click on an ad generated by Google AdSense, make note of their policies as follows:

 **Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies**

 _ **What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**_

The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.

 ** _Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie_** :

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative, or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time.

| **Share this page:  **  

What's This?

| | | |   
---|---|---|---|---  
| | |
